（忆往昔）
你没事吧
You okay?
有事
No.
我这辈子都在逃避猎魔
I spent my life running from hunting.
我从来不希望你和萨姆过这样的生活
I never wanted this for you and Sam.
仿佛昨天
Feels like yesterday,
我们还一起在天堂 而现在
we were together in heaven, and now…
妈妈 你想说什么
Mom… ‭w-what are you trying to say?
我得离开
I have to go.
妈妈的事
This whole mom thing, it's…
她回来了 却又走了
I mean, we get her back, and then she leaves.
我爷爷穷其一生
My grandfather spent the rest of his life.
去追踪一个什么修黎社
trying to track down something he called the Thule Society.
他们是个极扭曲秘密的社团
They were this twisted, secret fraternity,
想一统世界
Hell-bent on world domination,
资助过早期纳粹党
that sponsored the early days of the nazi party.
最后一页
This last page…
是所有死而复生的修黎社人的名册
Is a roster of every dead thule member who was reanimated.
他们就为这杀了我爷爷
This is why they killed my grandfather?
你个纳粹猪猡
You nazi pig!
艾萨克·巴斯拉比 他自燃了
One rabbi Isaac Bass… he spontaneously combusted.
怎么回事
What is that?!
混账纳粹
Nazi bastards.
上面写了怎么干掉他们吗
Anything in there on how to kill it?
如果你想让一名修黎社的朋友死透
If you want a friend of the Thule to stay dead,
得把尸体烧了
burn the body.
你们杀不尽修黎社
You will never kill all the Thule.
修黎社 万岁
Long live… The thule.
（如今）
（俄亥俄州 哥伦布）
有人吗
Hello?
劳埃德太太
Mrs. Lloyd.
你来早了
You're early.
我一向早到 在哪呢
I'm always early. Where is it?
只谈正事 我喜欢
All business. I like that.
1931年 纯金
1931. Solid gold.
瞧瞧这工艺
Look at that craftsmanship.
女士 如今可再不做这么好的东西了
No, ma'am, they don't make them like this anymore.
真美
Beautiful.
我带来了现金
I brought cash.
真周到
How thoughtful.
很遗憾 事情有变数
Unfortunately, there has been a change.
价格有变
In the price.
但是…我们说好的
But…we had a deal.
你说是「说好」
Well, you call it a deal.
我说是「谈判的开始」
I call it, uh, the start of negotiations.
有什么区别呢
You know, tomato, tomahto.
价格不能低于…
I-I couldn't let it go for less than, uh,
八万
80.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我没有 但是你们…
Well, I'm not, but you folks are …
对这些玩意如痴如狂
are mad about this stuff.
个人而言 我看不出它的吸引力
I mean, personally, uh, I don't, uh, see the appeal.
但如果你不想要
But if you're not interested,
我还是可以另找买家
I can always, uh, find a new buyer.
你知道你在跟谁说话吗
Do you know who you're talking to?
等其他人知道了我的遭遇
Good luck finding that new buyer when the community finds out.
看你还能不能找到买家
how I've been treated.
好吧 你的损失
Fine. Your loss.
等等
Wait.
那是怎么回事
What's that?
我不…
I-I don't, uh…
不 不
No! No!
天呐
Oh, God!
[邪恶力量 第12季第5集]
单子上的都买到了
Got everything on the list.
怎么样 炒还是炸
So what are you thinkin', scrambled or fried?
我现在不饿
I'm not really hungry right now.
你不…
Y-you're not that…
那馅饼呢
How about some pie?
待会儿的吧
Maybe later.
我正忙着呢
Kind of in the middle of something.
好吧 哥
All right, dude,
你肯定不对劲
something's wrong.
没有
No.
我懂的 如果妈妈…
I get it. If Mom …
你别说了
I'm gonna stop you right there, okay?
妈妈需要空间
Look, Mom needed her space,
我说过我不介意
and I told you I'm cool with it.
但你真不介意吗
But are you really?
昨晚发生的
Happened last night.
「两人丧身神秘大火」
"Two Killed in Mystery Fire""
神秘大火
Mystery fire?
嗯 只烧了尸体的那种
Yeah, the kind that doesn't burn anything but the bodies.
自燃
So spontaneous combustion.
你在想什么 女巫 龙
What are you thinking? Uh, witch? Dragon?
或许 看啊 这老妇人 超有钱
Maybe. Check it out. The old lady? Loaded.
史高治·麦克老鸭在钱堆里游泳的那种有钱
I'm talking Scrooge McDuck swimming in pools of money.
所以 这样的女人
So what's a lady like that.
为什么会凌晨3点去一间小破店
doing at some crap store at 3:00 a.m.?
上面写是古董店
Well, it says it was an antique shop.
所以呢
So?
有钱人喜欢买古董 我也不知道
Uh, rich people like antiquing. I don't know.
我们去看看吧
I say we check it out.
好吧
All right.
- 但是现在 你真不想谈谈… - 不想
- In the meantime, you sure you don't wanna talk about - No.
迪恩 这叫升华
Dean, it's called sublimation.
嗯 我就这样
Yeah. Yeah, it's kinda my thing.
（古董 收藏品）
看来我们错过了大部队
Looks like we missed the calvary.
那我们是不是该回家了
I guess we should go home then.
好吧
All right,
我猜那是第一位被害人
I'm guessing that's the first victim.
史高治·麦克老鸭女士
Scrooge McDuck lady?
嗯
Yeah.
那这就是那位古董商了
Which makes this the antiques dealer.
嗯 马文·布里克
Yeah. Name was Marvin Brickle.
鳏夫 这店开了几十年了
Widower. Owned the shop for decades.
没有硫磺
No sulphur.
没有电磁场
Ditto EMF.
巫术袋呢
Maybe hex bags?
嗯 也或许…
Yeah, or, uh, you know…
古董店 净是老物件
antique shop, full of old stuff.
或许这人拿到了什么受诅咒物件
Maybe the guy got his hands on a cursed object…
物件失控 就开始杀人
…and it went haywire, started killing everybody.
嗯 那也不是第一次了
Yeah, wouldn't be the first time.
是啊
Right.
迪恩
Dean…
- 伙计 - 别说
- Dude… - Don't say it.
或许还是什么都别碰吧
May…maybe let's not touch anything.
直到我们搞清楚这些东西会不会想杀我们
until we figure out if this stuff wants to kill us or not?
好啊 知道了
Yeah, I got it.
算了吧
No.
萨姆 我好像有发现
Sam, I think I found something.
两个被害人遇害那晚
It looks like the victims were meeting about.
似乎是为一块古董怀表见面
an antique pocket watch the night they died.
怀表
Pocket watch?
嗯 至少据马文的电邮是这样
Yeah, according to Marv's e-mail, at least.
萨姆
Uh, Sam?
嗯 稍等
Yeah, hold up.
听着 我黑入了马文的硬盘
Get this … I hacked into Marv's hard drive.
看来他在经营
It … it looks like he was conducting…
一个地下生意
…an entire underground business,
专门针对
catering to, uh…
纳粹疯子
Nazi nutjobs?
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
你最好来看看
Might wanna take a look at this.
嗯 你怎么…
Yeah. What are you, uh…
这…
That's, uh…
是啊
Yeah.
看来史高治·麦克老鸭女士
Looks like Scrooge McDuck lady.
以收集纳粹的破烂为乐
got her rocks off by collecting Nazi crap.
是啊 看来是的
Yeah, guess so.
据马文的账簿
Uh, according to Marv's ledger,
怀表是希特勒一名亲信的
the watch belonged to a member of Hitler's inner circle.
- 表呢 - 不知道
- So where is it now? - I don't know.
警方没有报告说发现怀表
The police didn't report finding it.
我要大胆猜测
And I'm gonna go out on a limb here.
表可能既不在外面
and guess that it's probably not out there.
也不在这里
and probably not in here.
嗯
Yeah.
跟纳粹有关
I mean…Nazi connection?
杀人模式
The immolation M.O.?
听上去耳熟吗
Sound like anybody we know?
修黎社
The Thule.
或许他们来搅局了
Maybe they crashed the party,
拿走了表 并烧死了在场的人
took the watch, and torched the bystanders.
纳粹
Nazis.
我真讨厌他们
I hate these guys.
这真好玩 我从不这样的
This is … this is fun. I-I don't really ever do this.
大家都说 「提防约炮文化 艾莉」
And everyone's like, "Watch out for the hookup culture, Ellie."
我觉得他们就是担心我
I think they just worry 'cause, you know,
因为我刚结束一段恋情
I-I just got out of a relationship.
但我把戒指还回去了
Um, but no, no, I gave … I gave back the ring,
所以…这是好事 对吧
so that's just … that's all … that's a good thing, right?
抱歉 嗯 我…
Sorry. Yeah, that was …
我还在摸索
I-I'm kinda still figuring out how the whole,
陌陌这玩意怎么用
you know, Tinder thing works.
没事的
It's cool.
嗯 但是
Yeah, but, like…
老实说 我可以更酷一点的
I could … I could be cooler, let's be honest.
因为 你的胡子太酷了
'Cause, you know, like, your beard, it's super cool.
你想喝一杯吗
Uh, do you want a drink?
嗯 我要去…
Yeah, I'm gonna … I'm gonna use the, uh,
洗手间
the little girls'…room and just…
好吧
Okay.
天呐
God.
得了 艾莉诺 他很性感
Come on, Eleanore. He is hot.
你要穿上「大姑娘」的「裤子」
So you just … you put on those big girl pants.
然后脱了他的裤子
and you take off his.
就是普通裤子啦
Well…regular pants,
也不是大姑娘的裤子
not big girl pants.
你们干什么 艾莉
What are you doing? Ellie?
[德语] 那姑娘
Das Madchen!
白痴 我们得抓活的
Idiot! We need her alive.
对不起 父亲
I'm sorry, father.
不要紧
Doesn't matter.
我们有办法追踪她
We have what we need to track her.
来吧
Come.
账簿我们已经进行一半了
We're halfway through the ledger.
我干掉了六个 泥人干掉了其他的
I nailed six, and the golem got the rest.
感觉很棒
It feels good, you know,
完成犹大计划开启的事业
finishing what the Judah Initiative started.
你爷爷会感到骄傲的
Your grandfather would be proud.
（德国 柏林）
是啊 大学辍学
Yeah, well, dropping out of college.
去消灭纳粹活死人
to wipe out Nazi corpse-bags.
并非我母亲的梦想
wasn't exactly my mother's dream,
但还能怎么办
but what are you gonna do?
你听说我们这边有修黎社活动吗
You hear about any Thule activity in our neck of the woods?
最近没有
Not lately.
这些德国混蛋都在父国活动
These Deutsch-nozzles have been sticking to the Fatherland.
最近
Lately?
嗯
Yeah.
他们集结了起来 很紧张
They're closing ranks. All jumpy.
知道是有什么情况吗
Any idea what's cookin'?
不管是什么事 很重大
Whatever it is, it's big.
我们找到了一些他们的文件
We got our hands on a few of their documents.
任务代号是「Das Blut」
Code named the mission "Das Blut" …
「血」
"The Blood."
听上去美妙的不祥
The… Wow, that sounds nice and ominous.
是吧
Right?
他们整个组织啊
I mean, we're talking the whole enchilada …
修黎社最高指挥都聚集在一起
the Thule High Command all in one place.
你知道有块重要的怀表吗
Hey, does the, uh, this pocket watch mean anything to you,
是纳粹遗物
Nazi-relic wise?
不知道 抱歉
No. Sorry.
又发现一具尸体
Another body just dropped.
亚伦 我们得回头再打给你了 伙计
Aaron, we're gonna have to call you back, bud.
等我们赶到 他已经烧成灰了
By the time we got there, he was ash and bone.
是什么能把人弄成这样
What does that to a human being?
还有别的发现吗
You find anything else?
只有尸体 另一个受害人很幸运
Just the body. The other victim was lucky.
她逃走了 跑去了邻居家
She got away, ran to her neighbor's,
报了警
and called for help.
生还者在哪
So where's the survivor now?
怎么了 我已经录过口供了
What's going on? I already gave my statement.
干什么
What … what is happening?
天呐
Oh, my God.
天呐 不不不
Oh, my God. No. No, no, no, no, no!
放我走 来人 救命
Let me out! Somebody, help! Help!
来人救命啊 放我出去
Somebody help me! Let me out of here!
救命 拜托
Help! Please! Please, please, please.
拜托 放我走
Please! Let me out of here!
救命 拜托
Help! Please!
看见了吗
You see that?
- 嗯 - 我们得追上车
- Yeah. - We gotta follow that car.
我一直想说这话
I've always wanted to say that.
你为什么这么对我 求你了
Why are you doing this to me? Please.
听着 你想要什么我都给你
Okay, look, look, I-I will give you whatever you want.
我没有什么钱
Okay? I-I don't really have any money,
但我祖父母给我留下了股票
but my grandparents left me stocks.
求你 告诉我究竟怎么回事
Just … just, please, tell me what's going on.
天呐 你就不能闭嘴吗
Oh, my God. Do you ever shut up?
天呐
Man.
你去哪
Where you going?
你不能把我丢在这里
You can't leave me here!
父亲
Father…
我抓到她了 我到了 都锁着
Yes, I have her. I'm here now. It's all locked.
这不公平
That is not fair.
我努力了 我真努力了
You know, I try with you, I really do.
但你总希望我能参透你的心
But you expect me to be a mind reader,
这太累人了
and it's exhausting.
父亲 我得挂了
Father, I gotta go.
家事最烦人了 是吧
Well, family drama's a bitch, ain't it?
走
Move.
如果你们不是警察 那是什么人
So if you're not cops, then what are you?
这世上有些不该存在的东西
There are things out there that shouldn't exist.
坏东西 我们杀它们 算是我们的工作
Bad things. We kill 'em. It's kind of our job.
你现在跟我们在一起最安全
Yeah, so your safest place is with us right now.
什么会伤害我
Safe from…
纳粹僵尸吗
Nazi zombies.
是巫师
Necromancers.
他们用血魔法让自己能几乎永生
They use blood magic to make themselves almost immortal.
几乎
Almost?
如果爆头 焚尸
Well, you shoot 'em in the head, set 'em on fire,
还是能杀死它们的
that usually does the trick.
这太疯狂了
This is completely insane.
艾莉 你看到他们怎么对你朋友了
Ellie, you saw what they did to your friend.
好吧 但是
Okay, but…
他们为什么要杀尼克 为什么要绑架我
why … why would they kill Nick? And why kidnap me?
这些问题问得好
Those are great questions.
你们这群混蛋要那表做什么
What do you tools want with the watch?
这一切跟她有什么关系
And what does it have to do with her?
你们杀了我吧
You're gonna have to kill me.
好吧 想…
All right. Want to, uh…
嗯 好 我们去走走
Yep. All right, let's go for a walk.
等等 不行 你们不能打死他
Wait. No. No. You can't just shoot him.
我当然可以
Oh, no, sure I can.
- 我经常这么干 - 天呐
- See, I do it all the time. - Oh, my…
你不会想看的
You don't wanna watch this.
好吧 好吧 别…
All right! All right, all right. Just…
那是我父亲的 纳哈斯指挥官
It belongs to my father. Commandant Nauhaus.
修黎社最高指挥官之一
Thule High Command? Ranking officer?
好吧
Okay.
这没那么难吧
See, that wasn't so hard now, was it?
继续
Carry on.
你不懂 他会杀了我的
You don't understand. He'll kill me.
你以为这是给你挠痒痒用的
What do you think this is, a tickle party?
是战争结束时开始的
It started at the end of the war.
（德国 柏林）
苏联包围了元首地堡
The Soviets had surrounded the Fuhrerbunker.
大家都知道已经没戏了
Everyone knew it was over …
除了我父亲
everyone except my father.
（还有别的办法）
好了 跳过前戏
All right, skip the foreplay.
你爸把希特勒怎么了
What did your dad do to Hitler?
他救了他
He saved his life.
他救了他的灵魂 不是比喻
Well, he saved his soul. Like, literally.
那表 就像魂器
The watch, it's like a … it's like a horcrux.
《哈利·波特》梗
It's a Harry Potter thing.
你当然会知道
Oh, you would know that.
总之 表装着希特勒的灵魂吗
Anyways…so the watch holds Hitler's soul?
好吧
Right.
你把希特勒的灵魂困在了一块怀表里
You … you trapped Hitler's soul in a pocket watch?
干什么 保存吗
Why is that? For safekeeping?
不 是为了复活他
No. To bring him back.
我第一次听时也觉得是疯了
It sounded bonkers to me the first time I heard it, too.
你第一次听说
The first time you heard it?
你当时没在场吗
Weren't you there?
什么 不 我是94年在水牛城出生的
What? No. Man, I was born in Buffalo in '94.
听着 「复活希特勒」的计划
Listen, this whole "Let's bring Hitler back"
已经由来已久了
is more of an O.G. Thule plan.
他们成天说个不停
All they do is yap about it.
他在开玩笑吧 这是玩笑吧
He's joking, right? Right? This is … this is a joke.
等等 咱们再回到
Okay, wait. Let's just … let's back up to the part.
你爸打算复活阿道夫·希特勒的那部分
where your dad is going to resurrect Adolph Hitler.
离开地堡后
After the bunker,
偷偷将希特勒灵魂运出去的修黎社特工
the Thule agents who were smuggling Hitler's soul out.
遭到了苏联人的袭击
got whacked by Soviets.
- 所以你们把表丢了 - 不是我丢的
- So you lost the watch. - Hey, I didn't lose it.
表落入了一个俄罗斯家庭手里
It ended up with some Russian family.
然后修黎社追踪它到了中国 然后是秘鲁
Then the Thule tracked it to China and then to Peru.
然后就到了那家古董店里
Then it wound up in that antique shop.
所以他们现在都群情高昂地想复活元首
So now they're all hyped to get their Fuhrer-resurrection on.
这不是开玩笑 天呐
This isn't a joke. Oh, my God.
他们打算怎么复活他
How do they plan on bringing him back?
希特勒的灵魂只能寄居在
The soul of Hitler can only inhabit the body.
拥有他血脉的人的身上
of somebody who possesses his blood.
他的血 Das blut
His blood. Das blut.
我理理清楚
So let me get this straight.
修黎社想把希特勒
The Thule want to upload Hitler.
上传到他一个亲戚的身体里
into the body of one of his relatives?
他还有亲戚活着吗
Do they even exist anymore?
那边就有一位
Well, there's one right there.
等等 你觉得我跟希特勒有血缘关系
Wait. Wait. You think I'm related to Hitler?
好吧 这太好笑了
Okay, okay, that … that … that is just hilarious.
你这辈子他们都在留意你
They've been keeping tabs on you your whole life.
修黎社追踪所有希特勒的后裔
The Thule track all of Hitler's descendants.
你碰巧跟表在一个州
You just happen to be in the same state as the watch.
- 多巧 - 不
- Go figure. - No.
不可能 我妈妈 她追溯我们家谱
No way. Okay, my mom, she … she tracked our family.
能追溯到五月花号
all the way back to the Mayflower.
- 她说 - 你是领养的
- She said - You're adopted.
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
你来自伊利诺伊州 惠顿
You're from Wheaton, Illinois.
四年参加马拉松
All-state cross-country all four years.
真会使用网络
Wow, way to use the Internet.
你学做医生
You trained to become a doctor,
但第一次看到尸体后就辍学了
but you dropped out at the sight of your first stiff.
我是在休假
I am taking a sabbatical.
你婚礼前两天逃婚了
You dipped town two days before your wedding.
他跟我们的餐饮商上床了 你…
He was banging our caterer! You…
你似乎特别喜欢跑
It seems as though this running is a thing for you.
我…
I-I…
瞧
See?
嗯 我去追她
Yeah, I got her.
- 我们得走了 - 我知道
- We gotta move. - I know.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
我给我妈发短信了
Well, I, uh, texted my mom,
问我是不是领养的
asked if I was adopted.
她说 「亲爱的 给我们打电话」
She wrote, "Honey, call us."
那人刚把我的生活搅得天翻地覆
That guy out there just flipped my life inside out.
就花了五秒钟
in, like, five seconds.
艾莉 我知道你现在大概是这么觉得
Ellie, I know it probably feels like that right now,
但你应付得来的
but you can handle this.
轻浮我应付得来
Being a little flighty, I can handle.
但跟史上最大的种族屠杀疯子有血缘关系
Being related to the biggest genocidal maniac of all time?
未必吧
I don't think so.
最近真是热得要命 是吧
It's been crazy hot lately, right?
全球变暖什么的
That global warming…
她就在附近
She's close.
我知道现在你很难相信 但是
I know it's hard to believe this right now, but …
会好起来的
it will get easier.
相信我 我经历过
Trust me, I've been there.
是啊 也有人想用你来复活阿道夫·希特勒吗
Oh, right. Did someone wanna use you to resurrect Adolph Hitler?
那倒不是
Uh, w… No, not exactly.
这不就是了
There you go.
但他们想要我复活路西法
But they did want me to bring back Lucifer.
我是他的皮囊
I was his vessel …
希特勒我差点就信了
You almost, almost had me with Hitler.
但路西法 不是吧 魔鬼
But Lucifer? Really? The Devil?
我不行 我做不到
I can't, okay? I can't do this.
好了 崩溃结束了
All right, meltdown time's over.
听着 你现在就得去面对
Listen, you need to face this now.
不管你信不信 我们现在占优势
Believe it or not, we actually have the upper hand here.
据那位小混蛋说
According to, uh, you know, Junior Jackass in there,
修黎社需要你
the Thule want you.
这我们可以利用 来做个陷阱
Now we can use that. We can set a trap.
你现在想用我当诱饵
Now you wanna use me as bait?
我们不是想用你当诱饵 艾莉 但是
We don't want to use you as bait, Ellie, but…
我们有机会一次性消灭
We have the opportunity to take out.
整个修黎社最高指挥
the entire Thule High Command in one shot.
听上去吓人吗 当然了
Now does that sound scary? Yeah, you bet.
但是有时候 你该跑
But there are times when you run.
有时候 你要留下抗争
and there are times when you stand and fight.
现在就是抗争的时候
Now is one of those times when you fight.
我们保证会确保你的安全
Now we promise that we will keep you safe.
天呐
Oh, my God.
开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
趴下
Get down.
- 他们在里面 - 嗯
- They're in there. - Yeah.
收到
Verstanden?
撤 她跑了
Ruckzug! Sie ist auf der Flucht!
走
Go!
艾莉
Ellie.
迪恩
Dean!
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
你好
Hello.
救命
Help!
她还是不接
She's still not picking up.
- 太好了 - 或许她吓到了
- Awesome. - Maybe she got spooked.
她不是就知道跑吗
Well, isn't running a whole thing with her?
我是艾莉 你知道该做什么
Hey, it's Ellie. You know what to do.
艾莉 还是萨姆·温彻斯特
Ellie, it's Sam Winchester. Again.
听着 我知道这希特勒的事让人糊涂
Listen, I know all this Hitler stuff is confusing,
但我保证我们能解释
but I promise we can explain it.
我们能保护你
And we can keep you safe.
给我回电话 好吗
Just call me back. Okay?
你怎么把希特勒的事告诉他们了
How could you tell them about Hitler?
- 我可以解释 - 被犹大
- I can explain - It wasn't bad enough.
和他讨厌的泥人追杀还不够糟吗
being hunted by the Judah and his revolting golem?
我只是在拖时间
I was stalling.
否则他们会杀了我 带走她
They would've killed me and taken her.
你该感谢我
You should be thanking me.
你本该是我的继承人
You were supposed to be my heir.
然而 你总是不断让我失望
Instead, you're an inconceivable disappointment.
我以前很敬仰你
You know, I used to look up to you.
你征服了死亡
You conquered death.
你做了那么多事 但现在呢
You did so many things. But now?
现在你只想重温跟希特勒的光荣岁月
Now all you wanna do is relive your glory days with Hitler.
你们这一代 千禧一代
Your generation … you millennials …
太软弱 无法掌控未来
are too weak to steward the future.
需要更坚定的人来掌舵
It needs a stronger hand.
这世界在分裂 燃烧
The world is divided und inflamed.
帝国的陨落 经济的衰退
This falling of empires, the flailing of economies,
所以说现在是元首回归的
is precisely why there has never been a better time.
最佳时机
for the Fuhrer's return.
你
And you…
亲爱的
…my dear,
你有他的眼睛
you have his eyes.
救命
Help!
谁救救我 救命
Somebody help me, please! Help me!
（家常菜）
好吧 肯定有追踪咒可用吧
All right, there's gotta be a tracking spell, right?
是啊 如果我们有东西可拿来追踪
Yeah, maybe if we had something to track.
那我们黑入城内所有交通监控
Guess we hack every traffic light in the city.
直到找到她
until we find her.
开始净化仪式
Begin the purification ritual.
已派侦察队去找温家兄弟了
A patrol has been sent to find the Winchesters.
很好
Good.
弗雷茨 我儿子今天累坏了
Fritz, my son has had a very trying day.
他该休息
He should rest.
什么 不 你干什么
What? Hey, no I'm … What are you doing?
放开我 混蛋
Get your hands off me, assclown.
你干什么
What are you doing?
父亲 求你
Father! Please!
我错了 我们可以听你的
I was wrong! We can do it your way!
父亲 求你
Father, please!
弗雷茨 你不用这么做的
Fritz, look, you don't have to do this, okay?
拜托
Come on.
听着 求你 你知道我是谁
Listen, please, you know who I am.
说
Go on.
弗雷茨 回话 弗雷茨
Fritz. Come in, Fritz.
温家兄弟的英帕拉停在一家餐馆外
Winchesters' Impala parked outside diner.
锯木厂路
Sawmill Road.
谢谢
Gracias.
有发现吗
Anything?
没有 我完全不知道该怎么找她
No. I-I-I mean, I have no idea how we're gonna find her.
就算我们…
Even if we look at…
如果你们想找到艾莉 就得保护我
If you wanna find Ellie, you have to protect me.
保护你
Protect you?
我们为什么要相信你
Why should we believe anything you say?
别去看
Don't look now.
街对面有个修黎社特工
Across the street, there's a Thule agent.
就在外面垃圾桶旁边
right beside the dumpster outside.
够了吗
Is that enough?
我刚杀了我爸一个手下
I just killed one of my dad's guys.
可能是陷阱
Could be a trap.
不是的
It's not.
你知道父亲是个
Do you know what it was like.
纳粹巫师是什么感觉吗 非常糟糕
to have a Nazi necromancer for a father? It sucked.
圣诞节别提了 学校职业日更是噩梦
Christmas was a joke. Career Day at school was a nightmare.
我一直只想让他骄傲
All I do is try to make him proud,
但我永远不够好
I'll never be good enough.
他叫一个叫弗雷茨的人杀我
He asked a guy named Fritz to kill me.
好吧 这是一点
Okay, well, there's that.
我们听你说完
We'll hear you out.
她在哪
Where is she?
我可以带你们去找她
I can take you to her.
好 你去开车 我收拾那德国佬
All right, you get the car, I'll take care of the Kraut.
好
All right.
去吧
Go.
那孩子到底还有点种
The boy has some spine after all.
我去找他
I'll find him.
克里斯托弗日后再说
Christoph's time will come.
现在
For now…
我们有更要紧的事
we have more important business.
你一直喜欢他
Ah, you always loved this one.
瓦格纳
Wagner.
让元首这样渐渐接受这新世界再合适不过
The perfect way to ease der Fuhrer into this new century.
她准备好了
She is prepared.
很好
Sehr gut.
- 好了 - 你干什么
- All right. - Hey, what … what are you doing?
等等 你们要把我丢在这儿
Wait, you're just gonna leave me here?
- 没错 - 什么
- Yeah, pretty much. - What?
好了 外面两个 里面不知道有多少
All right, we got two outside and who knows how many inside.
太好了
Great.
- 不行 - 为什么
- No. - Why?
迪恩 我们得悄悄行动
Dean, we need to be stealth, do this quietly.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
会有机会的 没事的
We'll get a chance. It's okay.
我们去杀纳粹吧
Let's go kill some Nazis.
你们在对我做什么
What are you doing to me?
元首的灵魂
The Fuher's soul.
必须占据一具
must occupy a body.
流着他的血液的躯体
that contains the blood of his blood.
你真以为
Did you really think.
我会让史上最伟大的人
I'd resurrect the greatest man who ever lived.
复活进入一个软弱
in the body of a weak,
配不上他的美国女人的身体里吗
unworthy, American female?
天呐
Mein Gott.
我需要的不是你
I never needed you,
只需要你的血
only your blood.
[咒语]
好
Ja.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
（等了好久啊）
希特勒
Hitler?
汉斯
Hans?
（你看上去真棒）
（一点没老）
沃尔夫冈
Wolfgang.
（你妻子怎么样了）
（她大概已经死了）
（过来 帅哥）
来吧
Come, come.
来
Come!
这不可能
This can't…be happening.
我的曾曾侄孙女
My great-great-grandniece.
谢谢你的馈赠 亲爱的
Thank you for the gift, Liebchen.
我们怎么处理她 元首
What shall we do with her, Fuhrer?
抽干她的血 然后喂狗
Take the rest of her blood, then give her to the dogs.
但元首 我们没有狗
But, Fuhrer, we have no dogs.
那就去找
Then get some!
我喜欢狗狗 汪汪汪
I love doggies. Woof, woof, woof.
沃尔夫冈 走吧
Wolfgang, come on.
真该带上榴弹发射器
Should've just brought the grenade launcher.
承认吧 你挺喜欢这样的
Admit it, though, you're having fun.
是啊 可喜欢了
Yeah, so much fun.
这不是年度最佳父亲吗
Well, if it isn't Father of the Year.
对元首放尊重点
Address den Fuhrer with respect.
元首
Fuhrer?
希特勒
Hitler?
Hitler.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam und Dean Winchester.
你们一定很重要 他怕你们
You must be important. He feared you.
纳哈斯 他还在呢
Nauhaus. Still up here.
真是件不错的新皮囊
A nice new meat suit.
这次有俩蛋蛋吗
It come with two testicles this time?
这是我喜欢的诸多升级之一 比如这个
One of many upgrades I'm enjoying. Like this!
就像把一个小戈培尔揣在我兜里
It's like having a tiny Goebbels in my pocket!
我卖掉了一千万本《我的奋斗》
I sold 10 million copies of "Mein Kampf."
你说我能在推特上掀起多大热潮
What do you think I can do with Twitter?
我的飞机呢
Where is my plane?!
就好了 元首
Almost ready, Fuhrer.
很好
Good.
我们怎么处理他们
What shall we do with them?
带上
Take them with us.
我会很喜欢把他们介绍给我新养的狗狗
I shall very much enjoy introducing them to my new dogs.
不 等等
No, wait. Wait.
不 我可以解释
No. I-I can explain.
让你再万岁
Heil this.
哥…
Dude…
你杀了希特勒
You killed Hitler.
是啊
Yeah.
太棒了
Awesome.
我杀了希特勒
I killed Hitler.
我觉得这一点足以让我一辈子免费喝酒了
I think that entitles me to free drinks for the rest of my life.
我要去印T恤
I'm gonna get t-shirts made.
你知道没人会相信你的 是吧
You know no one's gonna believe you, right?
但你信我啊 你可是在场的
But you believe me. You were there.
好了 走吧
All right, let's go.
等等 你们不杀我了吗
Hold up, you're not gonna kill me?
不杀 说好了的
No, we had a deal.
再说了 你有更大的麻烦
Besides, you got bigger problems.
修黎社的剩余成员将永远追杀你这个叛徒
The Thule that are left are gonna hunt you as a traitor forever.
对此的建议是
Our advice?
跑吧
Run.
你不如回水牛城吧
Why don't you head back to Buffalo?
没人会去水牛城的
Nobody goes to Buffalo.
你怎么样
So how you holding up?
我们刚刚火化了一堆纳粹僵尸的尸体
Uh, well, we just burned a pile of dead Nazi zombie bodies.
其中一个还是我杀的
One of which I killed,
所以这也许是我第三糟的一天吧
so maybe, like, third worst day ever.
我最近过得挺悲催的
I've had a rough time lately.
是啊 然后又发生了这一切
Yeah, and then all this happens.
但我觉得我会没事的
I think I'm gonna be okay, though.
我八成应该给我妈打个电话
I should probably call my mom.
不能再逃避了
You can only run for so long, you know?
所以 你觉得哪个更难一些
So, uh, what do you think is harder,
面对希特勒再生
facing the reincarnation of Hitler.
还是回去上医学院
or going back to med school?
我觉得我会选希特勒
I think I gotta say Hitler.
是啊 我也是这么认为的
Yeah, I think … I think so.
谢谢你所做的一切
Thank you for everything.
嗯 好好保重
Yeah. Uh… take care of yourself.
好
Yeah.
可以走了
Good to go.
我刚刚在想…
You know, I was thinkin'…
进城的时候我们经过了一家面包店
We passed a bakery on the way into town.
牌子上写着「方圆一千里最好的馅饼」
Sign said, "Best pie for a thousand miles""
你现在想吃馅饼了
So now you want pie?
我杀了希特勒
I killed Hitler.
我觉得我理应吃点馅饼
I think I deserve some pie.
我说过希特勒是我杀的吗
Did I mention I killed Hitler?
你要念叨一辈子了 是吧
I'm never gonna hear the end of this, am I?
大概是的
Probably not.